{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Brick \u0026 Concrete Patio Paver Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40879/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40879,"taskName":"Interlocking Pavers for Patios, Walks \u0026 Steps - Install","taskDescription":"Install Interlocking Pavers for Patios, Walks and Steps","xmTaskDescriptor":"Brick \u0026 Concrete Patio Paver Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":174,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"pavers paverse installation install interlocking","textMessagingName":"Install Pavers","rolloverLongDesc":"Interlocking concrete or brick shapes, of various textures and colors, forming a patterned surface for driveways or floors.","rolloverShortDesc":"Interlocking concrete or brick shapes, of various textures and colors, forming a patterned surface","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Replace or Install Concrete or Brick Pavers (Interlocking Brick or Concrete Blocks). HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated interlocking pavers contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Concrete \u0026 Brick Patio Paver Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Interlocking Pavers","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":40124,"bridgeTaskText":"Have an asphalt paving project? ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"Request an Asphalt Paving Pro","bridgeTaskLinkId":3578,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Interlocking Pavers for Patios, Walks and Steps - Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Interlocking Pavers for Patios, Walks \u0026 Steps - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Concrete Project","urlName":"Concrete-Brick-Pavers-for-Patios-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Concrete \u0026 Brick Paver Patio Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"pavers,paverse,installation,install,interlocking,concrete,patio,brick","emcCategoryOid":-12015,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1434,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40879/":{"taskOID":40879,"originalTaskOID":40879,"setID":1434,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7034,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Pavers","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where are you planning to install pavers? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10473,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10474,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pool Surround","answerDisplayText":"Pool Surround","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10475,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Seating area","answerDisplayText":"Seating area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10476,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walkway","answerDisplayText":"Walkway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10477,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home entryway","answerDisplayText":"Home entryway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7035,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10478,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New pavers for existing home","answerDisplayText":"New pavers for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10479,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New pavers for new construction","answerDisplayText":"New pavers for newly constructed home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10480,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replacing pavers for existing home","answerDisplayText":"Replacing pavers for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7036,"questionDisplayText":"Pattern","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In what pattern are the pavers to be laid?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10481,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Length-wise","answerDisplayText":"Length-wise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10482,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Herringbone","answerDisplayText":"Herringbone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10483,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Parquet","answerDisplayText":"Parquet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10484,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Random - irregular cut stone","answerDisplayText":"Random - irregular cut stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10485,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7034,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Pavers","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where are you planning to install pavers? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10473,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10474,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pool Surround","answerDisplayText":"Pool Surround","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10475,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Seating area","answerDisplayText":"Seating area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10476,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walkway","answerDisplayText":"Walkway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10477,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home entryway","answerDisplayText":"Home entryway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10473,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10474,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pool Surround","answerDisplayText":"Pool Surround","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10475,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Seating area","answerDisplayText":"Seating area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10476,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Walkway","answerDisplayText":"Walkway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10477,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Home entryway","answerDisplayText":"Home entryway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7035,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10478,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New pavers for existing home","answerDisplayText":"New pavers for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10479,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New pavers for new construction","answerDisplayText":"New pavers for newly constructed home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10480,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replacing pavers for existing home","answerDisplayText":"Replacing pavers for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10478,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New pavers for existing home","answerDisplayText":"New pavers for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10479,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New pavers for new construction","answerDisplayText":"New pavers for newly constructed home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10480,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replacing pavers for existing home","answerDisplayText":"Replacing pavers for existing home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7036,"questionDisplayText":"Pattern","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In what pattern are the pavers to be laid?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10481,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Length-wise","answerDisplayText":"Length-wise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10482,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Herringbone","answerDisplayText":"Herringbone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10483,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Parquet","answerDisplayText":"Parquet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10484,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Random - irregular cut stone","answerDisplayText":"Random - irregular cut stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10485,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10481,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Length-wise","answerDisplayText":"Length-wise","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10482,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Herringbone","answerDisplayText":"Herringbone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10483,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Parquet","answerDisplayText":"Parquet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10484,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Random - irregular cut stone","answerDisplayText":"Random - irregular cut stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10485,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}